let questions = [
  {
    question: 'The answer is really big? ',
    choice1: 'THE ANSWER.',
    choice2: 'Really big',
    choice3: 'An elephant.',
    choice4: 'The data given is insufficient',
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'Rate this app from 0 to 10',
    choice1: '0',
    choice2: '0.1',
    choice3: '0.14',
    choice4: '10',
    answer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'How cool is this quiz app',
    choice1: 'Amazing',
    choice2: 'vert bad',
    choice3: 'ugly;',
    choice4: 'Sucks',
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'what is the best app out there you can find online',
    choice1: 'Youtube',
    choice2: 'facebook',
    choice3: 'instagram;',
    choice4: 'this app',
    answer: '4',
  },
  {
    question: 'are you crazy?',
    choice1: 'Yes Iam',
    choice2: 'No',
    choice3: 'Nope',
    choice4: 'Nah',
    answer: '1',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the answer to the question',
    choice1: 'answer',
    choice2: 'What',
    choice3: 'is',
    choice4: 'I have no idea',
    answer: '2',
  },
  {
    question:
      'A man once said he went 35 days without sleep. How is that possible?',
    choice1: 'He is a legend',
    choice2: 'he has a condition',
    choice3: 'He slept at night',
    choice4: 'he drinks a lot of coffee',
    answer: '3',
  },

  {
    question: 'What’s something that gets wetter the more it dries?',
    choice1: 'A paper towel',
    choice2: 'water',
    choice3: 'dry water',
    choice4: 'water that dries',
    answer: '1',
  },

  {
    question: 'I wave, even if you don’t say hello. What am I?',
    choice1: 'stranger',
    choice2: 'me',
    choice3: 'you friend',
    choice4: 'A flag',
    answer: '4',
  },

  {
    question:
      'Two is a duo, and three is a trio. So what do four and five make?',
    choice1: 'forio',
    choice2: 'Nine',
    choice3: 'favio',
    choice4: 'fovio',
    answer: '2',
  },
];

export default questions;
